Daft Punk Unchained is a music, documentary film
directed by Hervé Martin-Delpierre.
Daft Punk Unchained is the first film about the pop culture phenomenon that is Daft Punk,
the duo with 12 million albums sold worldwide and seven Grammy Awards.
Throughout their career Thomas Bangalter and Guy-Manuel de Homem-Christo have
always resisted compromise and the established codes of show business.
They have remained determined to maintain control of every
link in the chain of their creative process.
In the era of globalisation and social networks, they rarely speak in
public and neither do they show their faces on TV.
This documentary explores this unprecedented cultural revolution revealing a duo of
artists on a permanent quest for creativity, independence and freedom.
Self, played by Thomas Bangalter.
Self, played by Guy-Manuel de Homem-Christo.
Self, played by Ye.
Self, played by Pharrell Williams.
Self, played by Michel Gondry.
Self, played by Paul Williams.
Daft Punk Unchained is an Anglo-French documentary film that was televised on 24
June 2015 in France and on 9 February 2016 in the United Kingdom.
It documents the rise to fame and personal lives of Daft Punk members Guy-Manuel de
Homem-Christo and Thomas Bangalter and their pioneering influence on electronic music.
The film runs chronologically through the artists' early years before their foundation of Daft Punk, up to the release of their 2013
album Random Access Memories and performance at the 56th Annual Grammy Awards, in which they won five Grammy Awards.
The documentary combines rare archive footage with interviews with Daft Punk's closest collaborators,
including Pharrell Williams, Giorgio Moroder, Nile Rodgers, Skrillex, Kanye West and Michel Gondry.
No new footage of Daft Punk was shot for the documentary.
The film explores themes of punk band, electronic music, music.